[Music]
4000 one ain't nobody getting my butt up
in
here ain't nobody my boy not me tell you
want to go to jail you going to go
home M M M M M
M you okay where we at well listen
Carrie drugged you try to have sex with
you and uh oh they think we committed
armed robbery so we're in
jail I don't like you no you like come
on come on take it to the hole what a
shot you are an ass aete she's an
athlete excuse me Mr policeman what are
you watching the Tulsa Shock Phoenix
Mercury game oh for real who win it
Mercury took it 1615 1516 damn they was
Bing with that man see that's your
problem cam you always playing you walk
up and down the street all day playing
stop playing if they didn't leave the
car this would have never happened they
the wantes that left the car what and
y'all the ones that made them think we
commit an arm robbery man I lost my
daddy watch while you trying to get your
dick with what wasn't no trying
cam shut up man you can't even swim I
know how to swim you can't swim swim
this B shut the up man he talking
to you I'm talking to all y'all he a
talking to me talk let me break this
down for y'all all I've done all day is
try to help y'all we got robbed by a guy
that keeps talking about sucking dick
today how do you think that makes me
feel hey Pang Clan just keep it down all
right hey who the you calling Pang
clam hey guys I have a gun okay and an
Evidence Locker full of cocaine so I'm
going to make it look like y'all did a
bunch of blow if you don't knock it
off looking like John
Candy
hello
really are you
sure again this has happened again you
know that
the well dorm boys dorm room
entertainment the dorm door door door
heads uh free to
go free to go that's my bad boo boy my
apologies for me and the police
department all together wait wait wait
wait wait wait what
happened turns out it was a white guy
this chick was like n there's a bunch of
black people bunch of black people so it
happens all of the time honestly so big
mistake that's my bad happens all of the
time guys so you see the
confusion ch
see you okay so sorry about all that by
the way it's
dormtainment thank you so much boss I
mean do entertainment is cool I mean
what that's all sir can can I be honest
with you can I be honest with you I
split a check between six other guys I
hello okay here's the problem the
goddamn cars that the goddamn told yard
and they tacked on another 350 bucks
come on
man this is so PornHub see that's the
girl from check cash store right there
hey
um did you call the cops on her I did
but only because I had to see you again
and this is special this is
something you're really
weird I'll get you guys a ride to the
tow yard and pay to get your car
out God I'm Kim and you guys are my
Kanye let's do
this yo Mike man did you see these
pictures of you on IG they're not good
bro it's not good look at
this come on man yo my girl is going to
kill me Rome this your fault man it
ain't my fault Mike shut your ass up ooh
the Gatorade dry hump picks on Insta
those were cool I mean I would have done
more but they were so cool I would have
liked it a million times if I could
[Music]
have
nah